Guide to the Frank Espada photographs and papers, 1946-2010 and undated, bulk 1964-2000 RL.00367
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Civil Rights and Community Activism, 1960s-1997; 3.5 Linear Feet 6.5 boxes Approximately 724 items
  - Finished Prints, 1963-1964, 1974; 51 prints
    - Voter registration drive, East New York / Brownsville, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0097)
      Image dimensions: 6 3/8 x 9 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0098)
      Image dimensions: 9 1/2 x 6 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0099)
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0100)
      Image dimensions: 9 1/2 x 6 1/4 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0101)
      Image dimensions: 8 3/8 x 5 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Learning to vote, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0102)
    - Voter registration, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0103)
      Image dimensions: 9 3/4 x 6 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Voter registration, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0104)
      Image dimensions: 6 1/2 x 9 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - A new voter, 1964 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0105)
      Image dimensions: 9 1/2 x 6 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Voter education drive, 1964 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0106)
      Image dimensions: 8 1/4 x 5 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Voter registration drive, 1964 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0107)
      Image dimensions: 6 3/8 x 9 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Voter registration, 1964 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0108)
      Image dimensions: 8 3/4 x 5 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0109)
    - Voter registration, 1964 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0110)
      Image dimensions: 6 1/4 x 9 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Voter registration, Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0111)
    - Voter registration drive, Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0112)
    - Michael at Thor Hotel, Mission Agenda SRO [Single Room Occupancy] Project, San Francisco, 1986 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0113)
      Image dimensions: 12 x 8 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Michael at Thor Hotel, Mission Agenda SRO [Single Room Occupancy] Project, San Francisco, 1986 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0114)
    - The Mission [Mission Agenda], San Francisco, 1980s (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0115)
    - Mission Agenda, San Francisco, 1980s (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0116)
    - Mission Agenda, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 8, Image RL.00367-P-0124)
      Image dimensions: 9 x 13 5/8 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Young man at March on Washington, 1963 (Box 9, Image RL.00367-P-0117)
      Image dimensions: 10 7/8 x 16 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - East New York, 1963 (Box 9, Image RL.00367-P-0118)
      Image dimensions: 9 x 13 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - School boycott, Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 9, Image RL.00367-P-0119)
      Image dimensions: 8 3/4 x 12 7/8/ inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - South Bronx, 1974 (Box 9, Image RL.00367-P-0120)
      Image dimensions: 10 3/4 x 15 7/8 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - East New York, Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 9, Image RL.00367-P-0121)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/2 x 18 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - During's Malcom's speech - school boycott, 1964 (Box 9, Image RL.00367-P-0122)
      Image dimensions: 7 3/4 x 11 1/4 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 18 inches
    - March on Washington, 1963 (Box 9, Image RL.00367-P-0123)
      Image dimensions: 7 5/8 x 11 1/4 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 18 inches
    - East New York, Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 54, Image RL.00367-P-0316)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/2 x 21 inches; sheet dimensions: 17 x 22 inches
    - Malcolm X, 1964 (Box 54, Image RL.00367-P-0317)
      Image dimensions: 12 1/4 x 16 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 24 inches
    - Malcolm's audience, 1964 (Box 54, Image RL.00367-P-0318)
      Image dimensions: 10 3/4 x 16 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 24 inches
    - Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 54, Image RL.00367-P-0319)
    - "Freedom in '63," Washington, D.C., 1963 (Box 55, Image RL.00367-P-0325)
      Image dimensions: 12 3/8 x 18 inches; mount dimensions: 22 x 28 inches
  - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1960s-1997; 676 items
    - New York
      - Contact sheets CR 1-33, missing CR 5, 1962-1970; 32 items (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Voter registration, Brownesville, E. New York, contact sheets 1-6, 1964; 6 items (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: Voter registration, Brownesville, E. New York, 1964; 26 items (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: East New York Action, circa 1960s; 35 items (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Solivan's campaign for State Assembly, East Harlem, contact sheets 1-12, missing 7, 1974 October; 11 items (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - ISH Campaign and Food Service, Betancourt Lunch Program and campaign, South Bronx, contact sheets 1-26, missing 10, 11, 13-17, 20, 23, 1985-1986; 17 items (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Work prints: Ismael Betancourt political campaign, Latin Belly, South Bronx (folder 1 of 4), 1975; 40 items (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: Ismael Betancourt political campaign, Latin Belly, South Bronx (folder 2 of 4), 1975; 40 items (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Work prints: Ismael Betancourt political campaign, Latin Belly, South Bronx (folder 3 of 4), 1975; 40 items (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Ismael Betancourt political campaign, Latin Belly, South Bronx (folder 4 of 4), 1975; 35 items (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Work prints: Ismael Betancourt Food Service Co., South Bronx, 1982; 21 items (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: Ismael Betancourt political campaign Bronx, (folder 1 of 2), 1982; 50 items (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Work prints: Ismael Betancourt political campaign, Bronx (folder 2 of 2), 1982; 17 items (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - California
      - Real Alternatives Program, San Francisco, contact sheets 1-30, 1985-1986; 30 items (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Real Alternatives Program, San Francisco (folder 1 of 5), 1986; 38 items (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: Real Alternatives Program, San Francisco, (folder 2 of 5), 1986; 40 items (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: Real Alternatives Program, San Francisco (folder 3 of 5), 1986; 38 items (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Work prints: Real Alternatives Program, San Francisco (folder 4 of 5), 1986; 38 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Real Alternatives Program, San Francisco (folder 5 of 5), 1986; 35 items (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - SRO Project, Mission Agenda, San Francisco, contacts SRO 1-18, missing SRO 4, 1997; 17 items (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: SRO Project, Mission Agenda, San Francisco, 1997; 26 items (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Quest International, Berkeley, Esperanza, San Jose, contact sheets unnumbered, 31564; 18 items (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Quest International, Berkeley, Esperanza, San Jose, 31564; 13 items (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Washington, D.C.
      - SAJA Benefit, Strawberry Hill, Robert Kennedy estate, contact sheets 4-16, Summer 1979; 13 items (Box 11, Folder 11)
- HIV/AIDS Projects, 1981-1992; 2.5 Linear Feet 4 boxes Approximately 665 items
  The HIV/AIDS and closely related street drug crisis compelled Frank Espada, living in California at the time, to document through photography the plight of affected families and individuals, and the many outreach programs supporting them. These include Y.E.S. (Youth Environment Studies), Sunburst, and other prevention and educational programs. Specific locations and subjects are described in the photograph or folder titles. Most titles are retained from the originals.
  - Finished Prints, 1981-1992; 24 prints
    - Youth Environment Study (YES) / Sex for Crack - Piri Thomas, San Francisco, 1985 (Box 12, Image RL.00367-P-0125)
      Image dimensions: 9 x 13 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 9 x 13 1/2 inches
    - Youth Environment Study (YES), Tenderloin, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 12, Image RL.00367-P-0126)
      Image dimensions: 9 1/8 x 13 1/4 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Youth Environment Study (YES), Tenderloin, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 12, Image RL.00367-P-0127)
      Image dimensions: 9 x 13 1/4 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Blonde woman with hands on face -- Star of David on right hand, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 12, Image RL.00367-P-0128)
      Image dimensions: 9 x 13 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Woman with dark hair and tear running down her face, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 12, Image RL.00367-P-0129)
      Image dimensions: 9 1/4 x 13 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Woman with long hair -- holding her face, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 12, Image RL.00367-P-0130)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - HIV couple, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 12, Image RL.00367-P-0131)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Black man with curly hair and oxygen tube in his nose, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 12, Image RL.00367-P-0132)
      Image dimensions: 9 1/4 x 12 3/4 inches; mount dimensions 11 x 14 inches
    - Gumercindo, former dock worker/organizer, San Francisco, 1981 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0133)
      Image dimensions: 9 3/4 x 13 1/2; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - Outreach worker with clients, the Tenderloin, San Francisco, 1989 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0134)
      Image dimensions: 7 7/8 x 11 7/8 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - Stephanie, Tenderloin, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0135)
      Image dimensions: 9 1/8 x 13 1/4 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - Stephanie, The Mission, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0136)
    - Felipe, The Tenderloin, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0137)
      Image dimensions: 11 3/4 x 17 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - Suzie, The Tenderloin, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0138)
      Image dimensions: 8 7/8 x 13 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
    - Tenderloin (AIDS hotel), San Francisco, 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0139)
      Image dimensions: 16 1/2 x 12 1/8 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 16 inches
    - Shirley Green, fire survivor, The Mission, 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0140)
      Image dimensions: 12 1/4 x 8 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 16 inches
    - John Henry, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0141)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/8 x 9 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 16 inches
    - Kathy at Mission Safe House, 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0142)
      Image dimensions: 12 1/2 x 9 5/8 inches; inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 16 inches
    - Doris, transvestite, The Mission, San Francisco, 1991 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0143)
      Image dimensions: 16 3/4 x 11 7/8 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 16 inches
    - Askia with client, Western Addition [Y.E.S. project], 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0313)
      Image dimensions: 9 3/4 x 6 7/8 inches; mount dimensions: 17 7/8 x 13 7/8 inches
    - Alfonso, San Franscisco, 1982 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0314)
      Image dimensions: 9 x 13 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
    - Amy and Jack, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 13, Image RL.00367-P-0315)
      Image dimensions: approximately 8 3/4 x 13 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 18 inches
    - Marilyn #2, the Tenderloin, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 54, Image RL.00367-P-0320)
      Image dimensions: 11 3/8 x 16 3/4 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 24 inches
    - Marilyn, The Tenderloin, San Francisco, 1990 (Box 55, Image RL.00367-P-0326)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/4 x 19 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 22 x 28 inches
  - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1986-1992; 641 items
    - O.S.Y. Youth Project, HIV/AIDS Prevention, San Francisco, contact sheets OSY 1-38, 1989; 38 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Work prints: O.S.Y. Youth Project, HIV/AIDS Prevention, San Francisco, 1986; 46 items (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Work prints: O.S.Y. Youth Project, HIV/AIDS Prevention, San Francisco, 1989; 132 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Youth Environment Study (YES), Sex for Crack, San Francisco, contact sheets 1-6, circa 1989-1990; 6 items (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Youth Environment Study (YES), HIV/AIDS Prevention Program, San Francisco, contact sheets 1-44, missing 6, circa 1989-1990; 43 items (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Youth Environment Study (YES), HIV/AIDS Prevention Program, San Francisco, contact sheets 45-96, missing 51, 53, 73, 79-83, 85, circa 1989-1992; 41 items (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Work prints: Youth Environment Study (YES), San Francisco, circa 1990-1992; 188 items (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Work prints: Youth Environment Study (YES), San Francisco, 1990; 42 items (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Crossings/Sunburst: Joey Benko and family, San Francisco, contact sheets 1-6, 13, 14, 1991; 8 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Crossings/Sunburst: Humphrey Garrett and family, Oakland, contact sheets 10-12, 15-20, 1992; 9 items (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Work prints: Crossings/Sunburst: Joey Benko and family, San Francisco, 1991; 54 items (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Work prints: Crossings/Sunburst: Humphrey Garrett and family, Oakland, 1992; 34 items (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Puerto Rican Diaspora, 1965-1989 and undated; 30 Linear Feet 41 boxes Approximately 12,323 items
  Images from the Puerto Rican Diaspora Documentary Project were taken by Frank Espada in over 30 locations throughout the United States and Puerto Rico in the 1970s and 1980s, chiefly from 1979 to 1981, although his interest in the topic began much earlier. The prints are organized by location: Boston, California, Chicago, Connecticut, Hawaii, Massachusetts, New Jersey, New York, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Puerto Rico, Washington D.C., and Wisconsin (Milwaukee). Reflecting settlement patterns of the diaspora, the largest series are Connecticut, New York, and Pennsylvania. Series include finished prints ranging in size from 8x10 to 24x30 inches, small work prints, and contact sheets.
  Subjects range widely. The dominant genre is the many portraits of men, women, and children of Puerto Rican ancestry, including individuals of mixed race. Topics explored through the photographs are family life in Puerto Rican communities; Puerto Rican-American culture and street life in large U.S. cities; education, drug rehabilitation, and job training programs; labor issues and Puerto Rican laborers, with one series focusing on mushroom workers in Pennsylvania; and human rights activism in the Puerto Rican communities. In addition to his work in the continental U.S. and Hawaii, Espada also traveled to Puerto Rico, documenting emigrants who had returned to their homeland.
  The Diaspora project was funded largely through a multi-year National Endowment for the Humanities grant; among Espada's papers in this collection are many files documenting the project's lifespan and its culmination in many exhibits, educational programs, and a book illustrated with many of the photographs, The Puerto Rican Diaspora: Themes in the Survival of a People (2007), also available in Duke Libraries.
  Of additional interest are over 100 oral history interviews conducted by Espada with Puerto Rican migrants, and three interviews on videocassettes about his work on the project; his papers also contain many materials concerning the oral history phase of the project.
  Arrangement
  Within the geographical subseries, the photographs are arranged by format, beginning with finished prints in rough order from small to large sizes (approximately 8x10 to 24x30 inches), followed by the contact sheets and small work prints, which number several thousand.
  Work or proof prints are typically sized 3 1/2 x 5 inches; there are also pockets of 5x7 and 8x10 inch prints which represent Espada's preferred images that he selected as he worked through the editorial process.
  Many work prints bear stamps on the back with the project title, theme, subjects, date, and original identification number.
  Specific locations, subjects and dates are reflected in the print titles and work print folder titles, as originally assigned by the photographer. In some cases, multiple date markings on finished prints may reflect the date taken and date printed.
  - Boston, 1980; 89 items
    - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1980
      - Nick Arana (folder 1 of 2), 1980; 40 items (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Nick Arana (folder 2 of 2), 1980; 23 items (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Raquel Ortiz, La Plaza, 1980; 26 items (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - California, 1976-1981; 832 items
    - Finished Prints, 1976-1981; 8 prints
      - John Santos, renowned musician and musicologist, San Francisco, 1980 (Box 12, Image RL.00367-P-0144)
        Image dimensions: 12 1/8 x 8 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
      - California: Pareja Tipica, celebrating San Juan Day, Cabrillo Beach (Print 255), 1976 (Box 17, Image RL.00367-P-0145)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/8 x 11 inches; mount dimensions: 13 x 16 inches
      - California: David Santiago, civic leader, chair of El Dia de San Juan Festival at Cabrillo Beach (Print 44), 1981 (Box 17, Image RL.00367-P-0146)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 11 1/8 inches; mount dimensions: 13 x 16 inches
      - California: Doña Lila Romero, early migrant (1926) to Arizona cotton fields (deceased), Oakland (Print 24), circa 1981 (Box 17, Image RL.00367-P-0147)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/8 x 7 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 13 inches
      - California: San Francisco (Print 248), circa 1981 (Box 17, Image RL.00367-P-0148)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 11 1/4 inches; mount dimensions: 13 x 16 inches
      - California: Tommy Chevere, second generation, at his auto body repair shop, San Leandro (Print 52), 1981 (Box 17, Image RL.00367-P-0149)
        Image dimensions: 11 x 7 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 13 inches
      - California: Salsa at Cabrillo Beach, San Juan Day Festival (Print 254), 1976 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0150)
      - California: Sonny Arguinzoni, spiritual leader of Victory Temple, a Pentecostal congregation, with Bible students, Los Angeles (Print 53), 1981 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0151)
        Image dimensions: 9 1/2 x 13 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
    - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1976-1981; 824 items
      - Dia de San Juan, Cabrillo Beach, contact sheets 1-12, 1976; 12 items (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Work prints: Dia de San Juan, Cabrillo Beach, 1976; 81 items (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - California, contact sheets CA 1-32, missing CA 16, 18, 19, 21, 24, 25, 30, 31, 1981-05-01T00:00:00+00:00; 24 items (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Work prints: California, 1981; 144 items (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 1 of 10), 1981; 40 items (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 2 of 10), 1981; 40 items (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 3 of 10), 1981; 40 items (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 4 of 10), 1981; 40 items (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 5 of 10), 1981; 40 items (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 6 of 10), 1981; 40 items (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 7 of 10), 1981; 40 items (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 8 of 10), 1981; 40 items (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 9 of 10), 1981; 40 items (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Los Angeles; Cabrillo; San Francisco; Oakland (folder 10 of 10), 1981; 6 items (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: Los Angeles Arguinzoni, circa 1981; 38 items (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - OaklandWork prints:, 1980; 46 items (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Doña Lila, Oakland, 1981; 7 items (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Work prints: San Francisco, Baile, 1980; 31 items (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: Edelmiro Hunters, San Francisco, Pionero, 1981-05-01T00:00:00+00:00; 10 items (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Work prints: Tom Chevre, San Francisco, 1981; 21 items (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Work prints: California, 1980; 44 items (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Chicago, 1980-1982; 517 items
    - Finished Prints, 1980
      - Chicago, 1980 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0152)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/8 x 7 5/8 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1980-1982; 516 items
      - Chicago, contact sheets CH 1-37, missing CH 2, 7, 10, 24, 1982-08-01T00:00:00+00:00; 33 items (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Work prints: Chicago (folder 1 of 2), 1982-08-01T00:00:00+00:00; 134 items (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Chicago (folder 2 of 2), 1982-08-01T00:00:00+00:00; 114 items (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Chicago (2) (folder 1 of 4), 1982; 50 items (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Chicago (2) (folder 2 of 4), 1982; 50 items (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Chicago (2) (folder 3 of 4), 1982; 50 items (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Chicago (2) (folder 4 of 4), 1982; 18 items (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Chicago (3) (folder 1 of 2), circa 1982; 50 items (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Chicago (3) (folder 2 of 2), circa 1982; 11 items (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: Cha Cha Jimenez, 1980; 6 items (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut, 1981-1982; 518 items
    - Finished Prints, 1981-1982; 30 prints
      - Hartford, 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0153)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 1/2 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
      - Hartford, 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0154)
        Image dimensions: 7 5/8 x 11 1/4 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
      - Hartford, 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0155)
        Image dimensions: 8 7/8 x 13 3/8 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
      - Hartford, 1982 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0156)
      - Hartford, 1982 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0157)
      - Hartford, 1982 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0158)
      - Hartford, 1982 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0159)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 3/8 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
      - Hartford, 1982 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0160)
      - Hartford, circa 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0161)
      - Hartford, circa 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0162)
      - Hartford, circa 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0163)
        Image dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
      - Savage Nomads, Hartford, 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0164)
      - Ricky, Savage Nomad, Hartford, 1982 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0165)
      - Young Nomads, Hartford, 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0166)
        Image dimensions: 8 3/4 x 13 1/8 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
      - Bridgeport, circa 1982 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0167)
      - Mercedes on her stoop, Word Street, Hartford (Print 151), 1982 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0168)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/4 x 7 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 13 inches
      - El Piraguero, Park Street, Hartford (Print 203), 1982 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0169)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/4 x 7 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 13 x 16 inches
      - David, Hartford, 1981 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0170)
        Image dimensions: 17 x 11 1/2 inches; sheet dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
      - Hartford, 1981 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0171)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
      - Hartford, 1981 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0172)